[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The gestation period of a cheetah is about 90-95 days.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Gold carats measure purity, whereas diamond carats measure this quality.", "correct_answer": "Weight", "incorrect_answers": ["Color", "Hardness", "Clarity"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "James Bond is assigned what  weapon in the movie Dr. No?", "correct_answer": "Walther PPK", "incorrect_answers": ["Makarov", "Colt", "Luger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the name of the Mississippi River, which originated from the Ojibwe word misi-ziibi?", "correct_answer": "Great river", "incorrect_answers": ["Holy water", "Fast river", "River of life"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Star wars character said, I killed them. I killed them all. Theyre dead, every single one of them.?", "correct_answer": "Anakin Skywalker", "incorrect_answers": ["Jango Fett", "Count Dooku", "Emperor Palpetine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who won the award for best actress in a leading role at the 75th Academy Awards?", "correct_answer": "Nicole Kidman", "incorrect_answers": ["Julia Roberts", "Halle Berry", "Diane Lane"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1993 movie was honored with a Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Picture.", "correct_answer": "Indecent Proposal", "incorrect_answers": ["Last Action Hero", "Cliffhanger", "Body of Evidence"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country was the 2000 movie Romeo Must Die filmed?", "correct_answer": "Canada", "incorrect_answers": ["United States", "China", "Mexico"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Deoxyribonucleic acid (DNA), the molecule of heredity, is doubled in what stage of cell division?", "correct_answer": "S phase", "incorrect_answers": ["G2 phase", "M phase", "G1 phase"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Miracle, what causes Rob McClanahan and Jack O\u2019Callahan to have a fight during an early practice?", "correct_answer": "An old college rivalry", "incorrect_answers": ["They were trying to impress Herb Brooks.", "A lost bet", "A woman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This doctor who can communicate with animals is portrayed by Eddie Murphy.", "correct_answer": "Dr. Dolitte", "incorrect_answers": ["Dr. Evil", "Dr. Strangelove", "Dr. Zhivago"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Its a Mad, Mad, Mad, Mad World, how much money did Smiler hide?", "correct_answer": "$350,000", "incorrect_answers": ["$225,000", "$425,000", "$100,00"]}]